Ryder was
just under three. Just under
three. I mean, I was
kind of begging, begging for
a diagnosis so that I
could get him diagnosed
I mean, I knew, having
three children before he was
born, you know, I knew
that he wasn't meeting certain
milestones. I mean, specifically language,
you know? And
a doctor kept telling me
to wait. Every child is
different, you know? I'm like,
I feel like he should
be talking. I finally just
begged enough so that he
gave me a written diagnosis.
But see, I live in
California and we have like
legislation that is specific to
special needs and dis- In
order for me to take
advantage of early intervention
things at the regional center,
which is where we go
to get our supports and
services, I needed a written
diagnosis. I think it was
more fear, but I mean,
with the help of other
parents, thank God, who helped
me early. It was another
parent who became my first
advocate. And then I wanted
to do the same thing
as I've grown and I'm
still learning and still navigating
this walk, but I've learned
so much. I met a
parent there like who told
me, no, you got to
go beg, you got to
beg for it. Go to
the regional center, go here,
do this. I'll come with
you. You know, just that
type of stuff. Knowing that
there is someone else who
knows a little bit more
than I know and who's
sort of walking the same
walk, you know? And that
was really why I did.
It started my foundation writers
room just to be able
to not gatekeep, you know,
and share what I'm learning.
And then we can learn
together, we can cry together,
vent together, you know what
I mean? I love that.
I love it.